so let's see if we understand the
relationship between smt and cache
behavior let's say we have a program
named a who's working set is 10
kilobytes and we have programs being and
see who's working sets are 4 kilobytes
and one kilobytes respectively let's say
our processor supports four threads
simultaneously in the SMT fashion and
has an eight kilobyte a level 1 cache in
this case we should run a B and C
together because all of them can run
simultaneously a and B together we could
run simultaneously but we choose to run
it after we finish a and B or we do a
and B for a wild and see for a while and
so on so pretty much we don't run them
simultaneously we run c separately from
the other tool the next option is we run
a without using the other three smt ways
then we run B and C in two of the four
smt ways but we don't run a together
with the other tool the next option is
run a and C together then be but don't
do be simultaneously using
multithreading when we are doing a and C
or do them one at a time although we
code around four at a time we choose to
run one at a time